AN NGUYEN

Full Stack Developer

About Me

As a research scientist, I have spent the last 10 years trying to develop cures for diseases that afflict humans. I've always followed my passion and consequently always aim for excellence in my career.

I am now looking to apply my experience in project management, communication and critical thinking as a web developer. I readily tackle new challenges with grit and determination, as always with a smile on my face.

Contact



annguyen@sydney.edu.au



github/pleathershaman



an.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Education

The Web Developer Bootcamp

Udemy	1010 1010
The Modern React Bootcamp Udemy	2019 - 2019
Master of Science University of Sydney	2011 - 2012

2018 - 2019

Experience

Molecular Imaging Scientist 2012 - 2018 ANSTO

ANSTO is Australia's primary research facility for nuclear science. In this position, managed and contributed to research projects that use nuclear imaging. I was independently running multiple projects concurrently and was the main point of contact for all correspondence and communication. I was also responsible for organising project-related administration such as contracts, budgets, regulatory compliance and non-disclosure agreements.

Research Assistant 2008 - 2011 The Save Sight Institute

My main role in this position develop new experiments to investigate the causes of a rare eye disease. In this position, I set up a pipeline for analysing the differences in protein levels in a disease model.

Skills

HTML5	••••	CSS	••••
JavaScript	••••	Bootstrap	••••
React	••••	Redux	••••
Jest/Enzyme	••••	Git/Github	••••
NodeJS	••••	MongoDB	••••
Problem Solv	ing	••••	
Project Mana	gement	••••	
Communicati	on	••••	

<u>Awards</u>

The Wenkart Foundation Grant A competitive scholarship valued at \$28,000 p.a. (AUD) awarded for Master of Science.

References

Available on request

Personal Projects

Kitchen Catalogue

Kitchen Catalogue is an online database that allows users to create, edit and organise their cooking recipes. It features a full-stack MERN application with connection to a RESTful API, email confirmation and password reset. Technologies used include, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: http://kitchencatalogue.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/KitchenCatalogue

React Color Picker

React Color Picker is a single-page react application that helps users design their own color palettes and view different shades of a particular color. This application was the cap-stone projects of the Udemy Modern React Bootcamp. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://reactcolorpicker.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/reactColorPicker

Inspiration Montage

Inspiration Montage is a small react application that shows users a photo gallery based in their search term. Featuring an infinite scroll and connection to the Unsplashed API, this program provides the user with visual inspiration on nearly every topic. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://inspirationmontage.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/InspirationMontage